http://www.uwimaging.com/privacy-policy

Shop All Products
AboutAbout Light & MotionNews & PressAwards & PatentsAmbassadorsBlogEventsAcademyCameraBikeUnderwaterSale & DealsPro & Edu SalesBike IndustryDive Master/InstructorPro Photo/CineEdu Sales – Camera
0
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.
Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
Cookies
We and our third party partners may set and use cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about our web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
About Light & Motion
Light and Motion demonstrates through our daily work, a commitment to building products with integrity. Our goal is to have our products considered the best at what they do, recognized as carefully considered, designed by users, and finished with a deep appreciation for craftsmanship and build quality.
Address: 711 Neeson Rd, Marina, CA 93933
Phone: (831) 645-1538
Useful Links
SupportDealer LocatorBecome a DealerDealer AssetsContact Customer Support
Follow Us
IG: Photo/VideoFB: Photo/VideoFB: BikeFB: UnderwaterInstagram: BikeInstagram: DiveYouTube: Photo/VideoYouTube: Adventure
Signup for News & Deals
Signup
© 2020 Light & Motion
Privacy Policy
We use cookies on our website to give you the most relevant experience by remembering your preferences and repeat visits. By clicking “Accept”, you consent to the use of ALL the cookies. However you may visit Cookie Settings to provide a controlled consent.Cookie settingsACCEPTPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non Necessary
non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
Other
other
Analytics
analytics
Advertisement
advertisement
Performance
performance
